<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="wifi">Wifi</string>
    <string name="drive_thru">Drive-Thru</string>
    <string name="mobile_pay">Mobile Pay</string>
    <string name="menu_favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="catering">Catering</string>
    <string name="order_out_of_store">Order out of store</string>

    <string name="no_stores_matching_filters">Oh no! There isn\'t a Bruegger\'s Bagels near you. Try searching a new location.</string>
    <string name="add_funds_confirmation">You\'ve successfully added $%1$.2f to your Inner Circle Rewards Card.</string>

    <string name="insufficient_funds">Sorry! You don\'t have enough Inner Circle Rewards to redeem the reward.</string>

    <string name="turn_on_auto_reload_hint">Turn on Auto Reload to automatically add funds to your Inner Circle Rewards Card. You can edit or remove your settings any time!</string>

    <string name="recommend_update_dialog_text">An update to the Bruegger\'s Bagels Mobile App is available!</string>

    <string name="accept_t_n_c_part2"><u>Bruegger\'s Inner Circle Rewards Terms and Conditions</u></string>


    <string name="no_store_close_by">No nearby locations.</string>
    <string name="your_order_will_be_ready_asap">See you in 10&#8211;15 minutes!</string>
    <string name="no_stores_on_location">Oh no! There isn\'t a Bruegger\'s Bagels near you. Try searching a new location.</string>
    <string name="no_stores_on_location_pick_location">Oh no! There isn\'t a Bruegger\'s Bagels near you that supports order ahead. Try searching locations for walk-in orders</string>
    <string name="error_message_age_requirement">Sorry, you need to be at least 13 to use Bruegger\'s Inner Circle Rewards. See you in a couple years.</string>
    <string name="terms_n_conditions_text">You are requesting that we continuously charge your credit/debit card associated with your account for the loading of funds into your Bruegger\'s Bagels Loyalty account. Your credit/debit card will be charged when your balance reaches the amount you selected. You are choosing an automatic renewal plan which will continue to charge your credit/debit card associated with your account until you cancel your subscription.</string>
    <string name="you_are_already_registered">You\'re part of the Inner Circle! We already have data for you in our system. Return to the sign-in screen and enter your email and password. If you forgot your password, select the Forgot Password link and we will get you what you need!</string>

    <string name="notification_channel_id">bru_push_notification_channel_id</string>

    <string name="program_name">Bruegger\'s Bagels</string>
    <string name="payment_type_text">How would you \n like to pay for \n your order?</string>

</resources>
